bargainstobounty.com 2019-12-12

# Privacy Policy • Bargains to Bounty

### **WHO WE ARE**

Our website address is http://bargainstobounty.com, operated by Bargains to Bounty Media LLC. You may [contact us here](http://bargainstobounty.com/contact/).

### PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT and WHY WE COLLECT IT

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

We use cookies for the following purposes:

  1. **Advertising/Tracking**  
_These cookies are used to display relevant advertising to visitors, as well as to track the volume of visitors. They track details about visitors such as the number of unique visitors, number of times particular ads have been displayed, the number of clicks the ads have received, and are also used to measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns by building up user profiles. These are set by trusted third party networks, and are generally persistent in nature.  
_
  2. **Functionality/Performance**  
_These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site._ _All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance. Without these cookies, certain functionality may become unavailable._
  3. **Strictly Necessary Cookies  
**_These cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms._ _You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will then not work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information._

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

**INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING**

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on BargainstoBounty.com. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behavior on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

**ANALYTICS**

We use Google Analytics to record information about the pages a user has seen, for example the URL of the page, time of day, device used, etc. The information that we collect anonymized and sent to Google Analytics for analysis.

Google Analytics mainly uses first-party cookies to report on visitor interactions on this website. Users may disable cookies or delete any individual cookie. [Learn more](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies).

In addition, Google Analytics supports an optional browser [add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) that – once installed and enabled – disables measurement by Google Analytics for any site a user visits. Note that this add-on only disables Google Analytics measurement.

Google Analytics also collects Internet Protocol (IP) addresses to provide and protect the security of the service, and to give website owners a sense of which country, state, or city in the world their users come from (also known as “IP geolocation”).

[See this page for Google Analytics security and usage of data](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245)

**COMMENTS**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser to help prevent spam.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The [Gravatar service privacy policy is available here](https://automattic.com/privacy/) . After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

**CONTACT FORMS**

Contact form submissions are kept for one year for customer service purposes, but we do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.

**EMAIL ADDRESSES**

We may collect your email address, but only if you voluntarily provide it to us. This may occur, for example, if you sign up to receive an email newsletter, or enter a promotion. If you have provided your email address to us, we promise to use it only for the purposes for which it is provided.  We will not use your email address to contact you for unrelated reasons. We will not share your email address with any third parties. If you are a resident of a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), we do not wish to receive your email address, and will delete it you have provided it inadvertently.

To assist with sending you requested information via email newsletter, we use Google Feedburner to collect and store your email address. You may opt out of the collection of your data by

  1. Unsubscribing (we will remove your data) and
  2. Contacting them using the instructions on their [privacy page here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us).

**EMBEDDED CONTENT FROM OTHER WEBSITES**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g.Pinterest, WordPress.org, etc.).

Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged into that website.

### WHO WE SHARE YOUR DATA WITH

The data collected may be shared with:

  * Service providers and others who help with our business operations and assist in the delivery of our products and services including, but not limited to, application development, site hosting, maintenance, data analysis, infrastructure provision, IT services, customer service, email delivery services, payment processing, marketing, analytics, and enforcement of our Terms of Service Agreement and other agreements;
  * Other users of the site to identify you to anyone to whom you send messages or make comments through the Services;
  * Persons or entities with whom you consent to have your Personal Data shared;
  * Third parties in order to prevent damage to our property (tangible and intangible), for safety reasons, or to collect amounts owed to us;
  * Merchants and payment processors;
  * and third parties as we believe necessary or appropriate, in any manner permitted under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence.

We do this to:

  * comply with legal process;
  * respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence;
  * enforce our Terms of Service Agreement and other agreements;
  * protect our operations;
  * protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you, or others;
  * and allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

We will never sell, rent, or lease your Personal Data to a third party.

### HOW LONG WE RETAIN YOUR DATA

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

Contact forms are held for one year.

### WHAT RIGHTS YOU HAVE OVER YOUR DATA

If you have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### WHERE WE SEND YOUR DATA

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

Third parties have access to your data as noted within this agreement.

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

We will retain your Personal Data for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law.

### **USERS UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE**

Our Services are not directed to and we do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with Personal Data, we will take steps to remove such data. If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data without your consent, please contact us at .

By using the Services, you are representing to us that you are not under the age of 13.

### **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

Bargains to Bounty may change this Privacy Policy at any time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy is indicated by the “Last Updated” date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. All changes are effective immediately upon posting. Please review this Privacy Policy frequently to stay updated on changes that may affect you. Your continued use of this website signifies your continuing consent to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

_This policy was last modified on May 24, 2018_
